Finding Aid for College of Literature, Science and the Arts (University of Michigan) records, 1846-2014
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
- Dean’s Files 1916-2008
  - 1958-1959
    - Astronomy, Department of (Box 118)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 118)
    - Botany, Department of (Box 118)
    - Chemistry, Department of (Box 118)
    - Classical Studies, Department of (Box 118)
    - Economics, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 118)
    - English, Department of (Box 118)
    - English Language Institute (Box 118)
    - Far Eastern Languages and Literatures, Department of (Box 118)
    - Fine Arts, Department of (Box 118)
    - Geography, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 118)
    - Geology, Department of (Box 118)
    - German, Department of (Box 118)
    - History, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 118)
    - Journalism, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 118)
    - Library Science, Department of (Box 118)
    - Mathematics, Department of (Box 118)
    - Mineralogy, Department of (Box 118)
    - Near Eastern Studies, Department of (Box 118)
    - Philosophy, Department of (Box 118)
    - Physics, Department of (Box 118)
    - Political Science, Department of (Box 118)
    - Psychology, Department of (Box 118)
    - Romance Languages, Department of
      - French Staff 1955-59 (Box 118)
    - Slavic, Department of (Box 118)
    - Sociology, Department of (Box 118)
    - Speech, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 118)
    - Zoology, Department of (Box 118)
    - Museums
      - Anthropology (Box 119)
      - Archaeology (Box 119)
      - Art (Box 119)
      - Budget 1958-59 (Box 119)
      - Budget, Preliminary 1959-60 (Box 119)
      - Exhibits (Box 119)
      - Herbarium, 2 folders (Box 119)
      - Paleontology (Box 119)
      - Zoology
        - Tehuantepec 1956-59 (Box 119)
    - Aa-Ak (Box 119)
    - Acceptances (Box 119)
    - Administrative Board (Box 119)
    - Director of Admissions (Box 119)
    - Al-Am (Box 119)
    - American (Box 119)
    - American Humanities Seminar (Box 119)
    - An-Aq (Box 119)
    - Appointments (Box 119)
    - As-Az (Box 119)
    - Awards (Box 119)
    - Baa-Bum, 9 folders (Box 119)
    - Budget 1958-59
      - Additional Appropriations and Transfers (Box 119)
    - Budget 1959-60
      - Preliminary, 2 folders (Box 119)
    - Buildings
      - Angell Hall and Additions (Box 119)
      - Needs (Box 119)
    - Bun-Bur (Box 119)
    - Bureau of Psychological Services (Box 119)
    - Bus-Caq, 2 folders (Box 119)
    - Calendar (Box 119)
    - Car-Chh, 2 folders (Box 119)
    - Center for Research on Conflict Resolution (Box 119)
    - Chairmen of Departments (Box 119)
    - Chi-Ck (Box 119)
    - Class of 1911 (Box 119)
    - Class of 1917 (Box 119)
    - Class of 1923 Award (Box 119)
    - Clippings (Box 119)
    - Col-Con (Box 119)
    - Committees
      - Academic Counseling Procedures (Box 119)
      - Academic Year Institute (Box 119)
      - Admissions (Box 119)
      - American Institutions Lectureships (Box 119)
      - Announcement (Box 119)
      - Barbour Scholarships (Box 119)
      - Calendar Study (Box 120)
      - Cellular Biology, Experimental (Box 120)
      - Class Scheduling and Room Assignments (Box 120)
      - College Relations (Box 120)
      - Conference Center, Kellogg Foundation (Box 120)
      - Curriculum (Box 120)
      - Dearborn Center (Box 120)
      - Examination Procedures (Box 120)
      - Executive Committee, 2 folders (Box 120)
      - Exhibit Museum (Box 120)
      - Foreign Language Instruction (Box 120)
      - Form B, Revision of the (Box 120)
      - Great Books (Box 120)
      - Herbarium, 3 folders (Box 120)
      - Heyns, R. W. (Box 120)
      - Honors Council (Box 120)
      - Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 120)
      - Keniston Lectureship (Box 120)
      - Language Instruction, Research in (Box 120)
      - Library (Box 120)
      - Master List (Box 120)
      - Midwest Seminars (Box 120)
      - Natural Science Study (Box 120)
      - Nominating (Box 120)
      - Planning (Box 120)
      - Radiation Policy (Box 120)
      - Religion, Studies in (Box 120)
      - Summer Session (Box 120)
      - Teacher Certification Code Revision (Box 120)
      - Teacher Education, 2 folders (Box 120)
      - Teacher Training (Box 120)
      - Unified Science Program (Box 120)
      - West Medical Building (Box 120)
    - Conferences (Box 120)
    - Coo-Dem, 4 folders (Box 120)
    - Deans Conference (Box 120)
    - Deans Meeting (Mississippi Valley) (Box 120)
    - Den-Dij (Box 120)
    - Development Council (Box 120)
    - Dik-Dor (Box 120)
    - Divided Appointments (Box 120)
    - Du-Eg, 2 folders (Box 120)
    - Education, School of (Box 120)
    - Eh-Ez, 2 folders (Box 120)
    - Enrollment Estimates (Box 120)
    - Equipment, Special (Box 120)
    - Examination Schedules (Box 120)
    - Extension Service (Box 120)
    - Fa-Fd (Box 121)
    - Faculty
      - Counselors for Freshmen and Sophomores (Box 121)
      - Counselors for Juniors and Seniors (Box 121)
      - Meeting Material (Box 121)
      - Minutes (Box 121)
      - Work Load (Box 121)
    - Fe-Fq, 3 folders (Box 121)
    - Ford Foundation Proposal--Research in Public Relations (Box 121)
    - Foreign Language Courier (Box 121)
    - Forms--Miscellaneous (Box 121)
    - Fra-Frn (Box 121)
    - Fringe Benefits (Box 121)
    - Fro-Grd, 3 folders (Box 121)
    - Graduate School (Box 121)
    - Grants-In-Aid
      - Fund for the Advancement of Education (Box 121)
    - Gri-Hd, 4 folders (Box 121)
    - Harlan Hatcher (Box 121)
    - Hea-Hoo, 5 folders (Box 121)
    - Honors Program (Box 121)
    - Hop-I, 4 folders (Box 121)
    - Inquires, Job (Box 121)
    - Institutes
      - Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 121)
      - Propositions Concerning (Box 121)
      - Public Administration (Box 121)
      - Science and Technology (Box 121)
      - Social Research (Box 121)
    - International Center (Box 121)
    - Isard, Walter (Box 121)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 121)
    - Je-Jz (Box 121)
    - Hayward Keniston (Box 121)
    - Laa-Leh, 2 folders (Box 121)
    - Leaves of Absence (Box 121)
    - Leaves--Junior Research (Box 121)
    - Lei-Levh (Box 121)
    - Library (Box 121)
    - Linguistics Institute (Box 121)
    - Lia-Mb, 5 folders (Box 121)
    - Masters (Box 121)
    - McD-Mh, 4 folders (Box 121)
    - Merit Increases
      - Academic (Box 121)
      - Non-Academic (Box 121)
    - Mia-Mim (Box 121)
    - Michigan College Association (Box 121)
    - Miller, Freeman D. (Box 121)
    - Min-Nd, 5 folders (Box 121)
    - National
      - Defense Education Act (Box 121)
      - Institutes of Health (Box 121)
      - Music Camp (Box 121)
    - Nea-New (Box 121)
    - Nelson, L. M. (Box 122)
    - Newa-Nn (Box 122)
    - Niehuss, M. L. (Box 122)
    - No-Nz (Box 122)
    - North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 122)
    - Oa-Phn, 5 folders (Box 122)
    - Personnel Office (Box 122)
    - Pho-Pn (Box 122)
    - Plant Department (Box 122)
    - Po-Pq (Box 122)
    - Policy--Miscellaneous (Box 122)
    - Pr-Pz (Box 122)
    - President's Report (Box 122)
    - Promotions 1958-59 (Box 122)
    - Promotions, Recommendations for 1959-60 (Box 122)
    - Publications (Box 122)
    - Public Relations Study Group (Box 122)
    - Q-Rat (Box 122)
    - Questionnaires (Box 122)
    - Regents Communications (Box 122)
    - Regional Science Program (Proposed) (Box 122)
    - Registration and Records--General (Box 122)
    - Rel-Ric (Box 122)
    - Research Grants (Box 122)
    - Resignations (Box 122)
    - Retirements (Box 122)
    - Robertson, J. H. (Box 122)
    - Ru-Sd, 6 folders (Box 122)
    - Science Advisory Board (Box 122)
    - Se-Sz, 7 folders (Box 122)
    - Summer Faculty Research Fellowships (Box 122)
    - Summer Session (Box 122)
    - Ta-Tg (Box 122)
    - Television (Box 122)
    - Th-Tn (Box 122)
    - Burton D. Thuma (Memos To) (Box 122)
    - To-Trh (Box 122)
    - Travel (Box 122)
    - Tri-U, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - U.S. Information Agency (Box 122)
    - University of Michigan Research Institute (Box 122)
    - University Senate (Box 122)
    - Vi-Wiq, 6 folders (Box 122)
    - Willow Run Laboratories
      - Executive Committee (Box 122)
      - General (Box 122)
    - Wir-Wt, 2 folders (Box 122)
    - Work Load (Box 122)
    - Z (Box 122)
  - 1959-1960
    - Air Science, Department of (Box 123)
    - Anthropology, Department of (Box 123)
    - Astronomy, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 123)
    - Botanical Gardens
      - Directorship (Box 123)
    - Botany, Department of (Box 123)
    - Chemistry, Department of (Box 123)
    - Classical Studies, Department of (Box 123)
    - Communication Sciences Laboratory (Box 123)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 123)
    - English, Department of (Box 123)
    - English Language Institute (Box 123)
    - Far Eastern Languages and Literatures, Department of (Box 123)
    - Geography, Department of (Box 123)
    - Geology, Department of (Box 123)
    - German, Department of
      - Department Chairmanship (Box 123)
    - History, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 123)
    - History of Art, Department of (Box 123)
    - Journalism, Department of (Box 123)
    - Library Science, Department of (Box 123)
    - Mathematics, Department of (Box 123)
    - Mineralogy, Department of (Box 123)
    - Near Eastern Studies, Department of (Box 123)
    - Philosophy, Department of (Box 123)
    - Physics, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 123)
    - Political Science, Department of (Box 123)
    - Psychology, Department of (Box 123)
    - Romance Languages, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 123)
    - Slavic Languages and Literatures, Department of (Box 123)
    - Sociology, Department of (Box 123)
    - Social Psychology (Program) (Box 123)
    - Speech, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 123)
      - Research Laboratory (Box 123)
    - Zoology, Department of (Box 123)
    - Museums
      - Anthropology (Box 123)
      - Art (Box 123)
      - Exhibits (Box 123)
      - Herbarium (Box 123)
      - Paleontology (Box 123)
      - Zoology
        - Tehuantepec 1956-59 (Box 123)
    - Aa-Ak (Box 124)
    - Acceptances (Box 124)
    - Administrative Board (Box 124)
    - Admissions
      - Director of (Box 124)
      - Procedures (Box 124)
    - Advertising Conference (Box 124)
    - Al-Am (Box 124)
    - American (Box 124)
    - American Council on Education (Box 124)
    - An-Ar (Box 124)
    - Appointments (Box 124)
    - Arts Center (University) (Box 124)
    - As-Az (Box 124)
    - Athletic Academic Standing--Reports, Letters, Information (Box 124)
    - Baa-Bk, 3 folders (Box 124)
    - Biology (Miscellaneous Correspondence) (Box 124)
    - Biophysics (Box 124)
    - Bl-Bz, 7 folders (Box 124)
    - Ruth Brown (Box 124)
    - Budget 1959-60
      - Additional Appropriations and Transfers (Box 124)
    - Budget 1960-61, 2 folders (Box 124)
    - Buildings
      - Angell Hall and Additions (Box 124)
      - Equipment Needs (Box 124)
      - Physics-Astronomy (Box 124)
      - West Medical (Box 124)
    - Bureau of Psychological Services (Box 124)
    - Caa-Caq (Box 124)
    - Calendar (Box 124)
    - Car-Chh, 2 folders (Box 124)
    - Center for Tropical Studies (Box 124)
    - Chairmen of Departments (Box 124)
    - Chi-Ck (Box 124)
    - Citizens for Michigan (Box 124)
    - Class of 1911 (Box 124)
    - Class of 1917 (Box 124)
    - Class of 1923 Award (Box 124)
    - Class Size (Box 124)
    - Clippings (Box 124)
    - Coa-Con, 2 folders (Box 124)
    - Committees
      - Academic Counseling Procedures (Box 124)
      - Academic Performance of Athletes (Box 124)
      - Academic Year Institute (Box 124)
      - Admissions (Box 124)
      - Airborne Television Proposal (Box 124)
      - American Institutions Lectureships (Box 124)
      - Asian Studies (Box 124)
      - Barbour Scholarships (Box 124)
      - Calendar (Box 124)
      - Campus Planning (Box 124)
      - Cellular Biology (Box 124)
      - Class Scheduling and Room Assignments (Box 124)
      - College Relations (Box 125)
      - Conference Center (Box 125)
      - Course Numbering (Box 125)
      - Curriculum (Box 125)
      - Deans (Undergraduate Colleges) (Box 125)
      - Dearborn Center (Box 125)
      - Detroit Area Study (Box 125)
      - Enrollment (Box 125)
      - Examination Procedures (Box 125)
      - Executive, 2 folders (Box 125)
      - Fees (University) (Box 125)
      - Foreign Language Instruction (Box 125)
      - Fresh Air Camp (Box 125)
      - Herbarium (Box 125)
      - Honors Council (Box 125)
      - Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations, 2 folders (Box 125)
      - Institute of Science and Technology, 2 folders (Box 125)
      - Institute for Social Research, 2 folders (Box 125)
      - Institution Cooperation (Box 125)
      - Keniston Lectureship (Box 125)
      - Language Instruction, Research in (Box 125)
      - Library (Box 125)
      - Medical School--LS&A (Box 125)
      - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 125)
      - Michigan Alumni Visiting Professorship (Box 125)
      - Moving Expenses (Box 125)
      - Radiation Policy 1956-59 (Box 125)
      - Religion, Studies in (Box 125)
      - Russian Studies, Program in (Box 125)
      - Space and Planning (Box 125)
      - Summer Session (Box 125)
      - Teacher Education (Box 125)
      - Teacher Training (Box 125)
      - Unified Science Program (Box 125)
    - Conferences (Box 125)
    - Cou-Crn (Box 125)
    - Criticism (Letters) (Box 125)
    - Cro-Dem, 3 folders (Box 125)
    - Deans Conference (Box 125)
    - Den-Dij (Box 125)
    - Development Council (Box 125)
    - Dik-Dt, 2 folders (Box 125)
    - Dramatic Arts Center (Box 125)
    - Ea-Eg (Box 125)
    - Education, School of (Box 125)
    - Eh-Em (Box 125)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 125)
    - Enrollment Estimates (Box 125)
    - Examination Schedules (Box 125)
    - Extension Service (Box 125)
    - Fa-Fd (Box 126)
    - Faculty
      - Counselors for Freshmen and Sophomores (Box 126)
      - Counselors for Juniors and Seniors (Box 126)
      - Counselors of LS&A Students (Box 126)
      - Meeting Material (Box 126)
      - Minutes (Box 126)
    - Fe-Fq, 3 folders (Box 126)
    - Ford Foundation
      - International Studies Project (Box 126)
    - Foreign Language and Area Programs (Box 126)
    - Fra-Fz, 2 folders (Box 126)
    - George, Edwin S. Reserve (Box 126)
    - Gifts and Trust Funds (Box 126)
    - Gor-Grd (Box 126)
    - Graduate School
      - Faculty Research Grants (Box 126)
    - Grants-In-Aid (Box 126)
    - Gre-Grh (Box 126)
    - Growth of College (Box 126)
    - Gri-Har, 4 folders (Box 126)
    - Hatcher, Harlan (Box 126)
    - Hea-Him, 3 folders (Box 126)
    - Honors
      - Council (Box 126)
      - Program (Box 126)
    - Hol-Huq, 4 folders (Box 126)
    - Humor Folder (Box 126)
    - I (Box 126)
    - Inquiries, 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Institutes--General
      - Public Administration (Box 126)
      - Science and Technology (Box 126)
      - Social Research (Box 126)
    - International Center (Box 126)
    - Japanese Studies, Center for (Box 126)
    - Je-Kh, 3 folders (Box 126)
    - Keniston, Hayward (Box 126)
    - Ko-Leh, 4 folders (Box 126)
    - Leaves of Absence
      - General (Box 126)
      - Sabbatical (Box 126)
    - Lei-Lh, 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Library
      - Council (Box 126)
    - Lis-Lz, 2 folders (Box 126)
    - Luncheons (Box 126)
    - Maa-Mar, 3 folders (Box 126)
    - Masters, 2 folders (Box 126)
    - McD-Meq, 3 folders (Box 126)
    - Medical School (Box 126)
    - Merit Increases
      - Academic (Box 126)
      - Non-Academic (Box 126)
    - Miller, Freeman D. (Box 126)
    - Mia-Mim (Box 126)
    - Mississippi Valley Deans Conference (Box 126)
    - Min-Nd, 5 folders (Box 126)
    - National Defense Education Act (Box 126)
    - National (Box 127)
      - Institutes of Health (Box 127)
      - Music Camp (Box 127)
      - Science Foundation (Box 127)
    - Nea-New (Box 127)
    - Nelson, L. M. (Box 127)
    - News Service (Box 127)
    - Newa-Nn (Box 127)
    - Niehuss, M. L. (Box 127)
    - No-Nz (Box 127)
    - Nominating Committee (Box 127)
    - North Central Association of Colleges and Secondary Schools (Box 127)
    - Oa-Oz, 2 folders (Box 127)
    - Operations Research Department 1956-59 (Box 127)
    - Paa-Phn, 3 folders (Box 127)
    - Personnel Office (Box 127)
    - Pho-Pn (Box 127)
    - Plant Department (Box 127)
    - Po-Pq (Box 127)
    - Policy (Miscellaneous) (Box 127)
    - Pr-Pz (Box 127)
    - President's Report (Box 127)
    - Program for Appointments of Instructors and Assistant Professors (Box 127)
    - Project Michigan 1956-59 (Box 127)
    - Promotions 1959-60 (Box 127)
    - Promotions, Recommendations for 1960-61 (Box 127)
    - Publications (Box 127)
    - Q-Rat (Box 127)
    - Questionnaires (Box 127)
    - Rau-Rek (Box 127)
    - Real Estate (Box 127)
    - Regents Communications (Box 127)
    - Regents' Outstanding Achievement Award (Box 127)
    - Registration and Records (Box 127)
    - Rel-Ric (Box 127)
    - Repertory Theatre (Steering Committee) (Box 127)
    - Research Projects (Box 127)
    - Retirements (Box 127)
    - Robertson, J. H. (Box 127)
    - Ru-Rz (Box 127)
    - Russian Exchange Program (Box 127)
    - Saa-Sam (Box 127)
    - Salaries (Box 127)
    - San-Scg (Box 127)
    - Sawyer, Ralph A. (Vice-President) (Box 127)
    - Scha-Schl (Box 127)
    - Science Advisory Board (Box 127)
    - Se-Shd (Box 127)
    - Senate, University (Box 127)
    - She-Sph, 4 folders (Box 127)
    - Space Needs (Box 127)
    - Spi-Sz, 4 folders (Box 127)
    - Summer Faculty Research Fellowships (Box 127)
    - Summer Session (Box 127)
    - Ta-U, 3 folders (Box 127)
    - Television (Box 127)
    - Th-Tn (Box 127)
    - Theatre (Miscellaneous Correspondence) (Box 127)
    - To-Trh (Box 127)
    - Travel (Box 127)
    - U.S. Information Agency (Box 128)
    - University of Michigan Research Institute
      - Executive Committee, 2 folders (Box 128)
    - Va-Wam, 3 folders (Box 128)
    - Walter, Erich A. (Box 128)
    - Wan-Wiq, 6 folders (Box 128)
    - Willow Run Laboratories
      - Executive Committee (Box 128)
      - General (Box 128)
      - Permanent (Box 128)
    - Wir-Wt, 2 folders (Box 128)
  - 1960-1961
    - Air Science, Department of (Box 128)
    - Anthropology, Department of (Box 128)
    - Astronomy, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 128)
    - Botanical Gardens (Box 128)
    - Botany, Department of (Box 128)
    - Chemistry, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 128)
    - Classical Studies, Department of (Box 128)
    - Communication Sciences Laboratory (Box 128)
    - Economics, Department of (Box 128)
    - English, Department of (Box 128)
    - English Language Institute (Box 128)
    - Far Eastern Languages and Literatures, Department of (Box 128)
    - Geography, Department of (Box 128)
    - Geology, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 128)
    - German, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 128)
    - History, Department of (Box 128)
    - History of Art, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 128)
    - Journalism, Department of (Box 128)
    - Language Laboratory (Box 128)
    - Library Science, Department of (Box 128)
    - Mathematics, Department of (Box 129)
    - Mineralogy, Department of (Box 129)
    - Near Eastern Studies, Department of (Box 129)
    - Philosophy, Department of (Box 129)
    - Physics, Department of (Box 129)
    - Political Science, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 129)
    - Psychology, Department of (Box 129)
    - Romance Languages, Department of (Box 129)
    - Slavic Languages and Literatures, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 129)
    - Sociology, Department of
      - Chairmanship (Box 129)
    - Social Psychology (Program) (Box 129)
    - Speech, Department of (Box 129)
    - Zoology, Department of (Box 129)
    - Museums
      - Archaeology (Box 129)
      - Anthropology (Box 129)
      - Art (Box 129)
      - Exhibit (Box 129)
      - Herbarium (Box 129)
      - Laboratory of Vertebrate Biology (Box 129)
      - Paleontology (Box 129)
      - Zoology
        - Directorship (Box 129)
    - A (Box 129)
    - Acceptances (Box 129)
    - Administrative Board (Box 129)
    - Admissions
      - Director of (Box 129)
      - Procedures (Box 129)
    - Adult Education, Division of (Box 129)
    - American Council on Education (Box 129)
    - Appointments (Box 129)
    - Athletic Academic Standing--Reports, Letters, Information 1959-61 (Box 129)
    - Awards (Master File) (Box 129)
    - B (Box 129)
    - Bi (Box 129)
    - Br (Box 129)
    - Budget 1960-61 (Box 129)
    - Budget 1961-62 (Box 129)
    - Buildings
      - Angell Hall and Additions (Box 129)
      - Equipment Needs (Box 129)
      - Needs (5 Year Study) (Box 129)
      - Physics and Astronomy (Box 129)
    - Bureau of Psychological Services (Box 129)
    - C (Box 129)
    - Calendar
      - Discussions (Box 129)
    - Center (Box 130)
      - Higher Education, Study of (Box 130)
      - Tropical Studies (Box 130)
    - Chairmen of Departments (Box 130)
    - Class of 1911
      - 1917 (Box 130)
      - 1923 Award (Box 130)
    - Clippings (Box 130)
    - Co (Box 130)
    - Committees, 3 folders
      - Admissions (Box 130)
      - Airborne Television Proposal (Box 130)
      - American Institutions Lectureship and Professorship (Box 130)
      - Barbour Scholarships (Box 130)
      - Biophysics (Box 130)
      - Calendar 1958-62 (Box 130)
      - Campus Planning and Development (Box 130)
      - Class Scheduling and Room Assignment (Box 130)
      - College Relations (Box 130)
      - Course Numbering (Box 130)
      - Deans (Box 130)
      - Dearborn Center (Box 130)
      - Detroit Area Study (Box 130)
      - Executive Committee, 2 folders (Box 130)
      - Final Examination Scheduling (Box 130)
      - Honors Council (Box 130)
      - Institute of Labor and Industrial Relations (Box 130)
      - Institute of Science and Technology (Box 130)
      - Institute for Social Research (Box 130)
      - Institutional Cooperation (Box 130)
      - Junior Year Abroad (Box 130)
      - Library (Box 130)
      - Linguistic Activities, Organization of (Box 130)
      - Mental Health Research Institute (Box 130)
      - Midwest Terminal Conference (Box 130)
      - National Training Laboratories (Box 130)
      - Nominating, 2 folders (Box 130)
      - Office of Research Administration (Box 130)
      - Bureau of Public Health Economics (Box 130)
      - Studies in Religion (Box 131)
      - Revision--Form B (Box 131)
      - Space and Planning (Box 131)
      - Sponsored Research Fellowships (Box 131)
      - Student Opinion of Courses and Teaching (Box 131)
      - Summer Session (Box 131)
      - Teacher Education (Box 131)
      - Teacher Training (Box 131)
      - University of Michigan Research Institute (Box 131)
      - Willow Run Laboratories (Box 131)
      - Writing Skills, Improvement of (Box 131)
    - Conferences (Box 131)
    - Criticism (Letters) (Box 131)
    - D (Box 131)
    - Danforth Foundation (Box 131)
    - Deans' Conference (Box 131)
    - Development Council (Box 131)
    - Do (Box 131)
    - E (Box 131)
    - Education, School of (Box 131)
    - Engineering, College of (Box 131)
    - Examination Schedules (Box 131)
    - Extension Service
      - Correspondence Survey (Box 131)
    - F (Box 131)
    - Faculty
      - Counselors for Freshmen and Sophomores (Box 131)
      - Counselors for Juniors and Seniors (Box 131)
      - Counselors of LS&A Students (Box 131)
      - Directory Material (Box 131)
      - Meeting Material (Box 131)
      - Minutes (Box 131)
      - Work Load (Box 131)
    - Foreign Language and Area Programs (Box 131)